Hello, everyone.
Ciao a tutti.
I'm so glad that you are here.
Sono così felice che tu sia qui.
Welcome to my course, complete Linux training course to get your dream it job.
Benvenuto nel mio corso, completa il corso di formazione su Linux per ottenere il lavoro dei tuoi sogni.
Now, let me put it in a very simple way.
Ora, lasciatemi descrivere in modo molto semplice.
When you take this course, you will learn so many things about Linux that you're going to be able to
Quando seguirai questo corso, imparerai così tante cose su Linux che sarai in grado di candidarti
apply for a Linux job and you will get the job.
per un lavoro Linux e otterrai il lavoro.
Fair enough.
Giusto.
My name is Imran Afsal and I've been in it specifically in Linux field for more than two decades now.
Mi chiamo Imran Afsal e ci lavoro specificatamente nel campo Linux da più di due decenni.
I have actually worked in New York City for fashion industry, for tech media firms, for financial
In realtà ho lavorato a New York City per l'industria della moda, per società di media tecnologici, per società finanziarie,
firms, for cloud and hosting companies, you name it.
per società di cloud e hosting, lo chiami.
I did complete my bachelors in Computer Information Systems from Baruch College, City University of
Ho completato i miei corsi di laurea in Computer Information Systems al Baruch College, City University di New York
New York and my MBA from New York Institute of Technology.
e il mio MBA presso il New York Institute of Technology.
I teach in a very simple language, and I don't assume that you know a little bit more about Linux.
Insegno in un linguaggio molto semplice e non presumo che tu sappia qualcosa di più su Linux.
I will actually hold your hand every step of the way throughout this course, and I will make sure you
Ti terrò per mano in ogni fase del corso e mi assicurerò che
understand everything.
tu capisca tutto.
There are so many of my students here on Udemy who actually took this course and they were able to pass
Ci sono così tanti dei miei studenti qui su Udemy che hanno effettivamente seguito questo corso e sono stati in
any of the Linux certification and they were able to get the job of their dreams.
grado di superare qualsiasi certificazione Linux e sono stati in grado di ottenere il lavoro dei loro sogni.
So what are you waiting for?
Allora, cosa stai aspettando?
Let's go ahead and enroll.
Andiamo avanti e iscriviamoci.